tiertime.com 2019-11-30

# Tiertime Privacy Policy

**Effective Date: May 25, 2018**

Tiertime values your privacy, and appreciates your trust in us by putting your personal information in our Product. We understand how important the Data is, and we are committed to protecting your privacy and creating the best experience for you using our Product.

This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains our policies and procedures on what information Tiertime and its affiliated companies (Collectively, “Tiertime” or “we” and sometimes “us”) collect, use, disclose, and share your personal information or personal data (collectively, the “Data”), and why, what we may do with the Data, your options, your actions and possible consequences.

This Privacy Policy applies to the information obtained by us through your use of the Tiertime’s Product, which include hardware (including, without limitation, desktop 3D printers, industrial 3D printers, and etc, collectively, the “Hardware”), software (include, without limitation, “UP”, “UP Studio”, “Model Wizard”, and etc, collectively, the “Software”, websites (include, without limitation, “www.tiertime.com”, “www.cetus3d.com” and etc., collectively, the “Websites”), services (include, without limitation, Technical Support, 3D Printing Services, and etc., collectively, the “Service” and other products manufactured by Tiertime (collectively, the “Product”).

This Privacy Policy applies immediately to new users who starts using our Product on or after the Effective Day or on the Effective Data to users who used Product before the Effective Day.

If you have any questions regarding the Privacy Policy, please contact us by sending us email through privacy@tiertime.net.

## Will This Privacy Policy Ever Change?

As Tiertime evolves, we may need to update this Policy to keep pace with changes in our Product, our business and laws from different countries applicable to us and you; we will, however, always maintain our commitment to respect your privacy. We will post any revisions to this Policy, along with their effective date, in an easy to find area of our web site, so we recommend that you periodically check back here to stay informed of any changes. We will ask for your consent to such changes if required by applicable law; in other cases, please note that your continued use of Tiertime’s Product after any change means that you agree with, and consent to be bound by, the new Privacy Policy. If you disagree with any changes in this Policy and do not wish your information to be subject to the revised Policy, you will need to stop using Tiertime’s Product, and close your account if you already have one.

## I. Information Collection and Use

### What Information Does Tiertime Collect About Me and Why?

Tiertime collects Personal Data when you directly provide it to us (Such as when you register your accounts in our Websites), when 3rd Party provides us (3rd party might be our integration partners), or when you are using our Products or on our Websites.

The following table explains what Personal Data we collect, and why we collect it:

**We collect** | **Why we collect it**  
---|---  
Your username, email address and contact preferences | · To create and support your Tiertime Service account.  
· To communicate with you.  
· To enable other users to collaborate with you through Tiertime’s website and software.  
· To send you marketing emails and special offers, unless you opt-out.  
· To verify your email address to help prevent spam, fraud and abuse.  
Your name, image and other personal information, if you elect to share it | · To show in your user profile.  
· To ship the products you purchased from Websites  
The geographic area where you use your computing devices when you interact with the Service and the language you select | ·To localize your interaction with the Product and improve our understanding of how users interact with the Product.  
·To help you verify use of your account: We may make recent IP address history available to you through your account settings.  
·To assist us in complying with legal restrictions that may limit the permissible use of the Product.  
·To provide better collection of community data that we would like to share with all of our users.  
Your Device ID (Tiertime 3D Printer Serial Number) | · To show you statistical information based on the device usage.  
· To allow you to redeem certain promotional offer.  
· To provide technical support.  
· To distinguish multiple machines that you may have.  
Your Contact Telephone Number – if you elect to share | · To help prevent spam, fraud, and abuse, and to aid in account recovery.  
· If you elect to otherwise share your telephone number or link it to your account, it may also be shown in your user profile.  
Your location, calendar or time information – if you elect to share it | · To enhance location and calendar information.  
· To show you statistical information.  
User activity data regarding the print job, the print process, and the results of the print job. For example: print options, filament consumption, print job duration, status, and etc. 

You can elect not sharing personal data. Choose menu Option, and turn the Privacy Policy option off. The personal information will be removed from the data.

| · To provide better Product and User Experience.  
· To provide user the statistical data of her/his own use of the Product and Service  
· To provide better collection of community data for all the users of 3D Printer.  
· To enable other users to collaborate with you through Tiertime’s website and software.  
Data you uploaded. For example: Forum on Tiertime.com | · To provide better Product and Service  
· To provide stat, search and sharing services.  
· To provide better community service.  
· To enable other users to collaborate with you through Tiertime’s website and software.  
Activation Information | · To provide better Product and Service  
· To provide stat, search and sharing services.  
Your payment information | · To process your payment. (In most cases, Tiertime uses third-party payment processors and therefore has only limited information about your payment transactions)  
  
3D printing is relatively new for non-experts, especially for desktop 3D printing. There are many hurdles that Tiertime has committed to conquer, and we need help from all our users. Providing user activity data is one way of helping us, especially for the user activity data related to print job, and print process, which can help us produce better understand user behaviors and in return, we can produce better product, and provide better services.

If you visit a Tiertime website:

**We collect** | **Why we collect it**  
---|---  
Your email address (if you provide it) | ·To help you create a Tiertime service account.  
· To communicate with you.  
Tracking information | Please see the section on cookie and tracking below  
  
Finally, when you access the Service via a Tiertime Software application, that application will request access to certain information on your computing device.

### What Tracking Information Does Tiertime Collect About Me Or My Devices?

Tiertime uses cookies, tracking pixels and similar technologies on our Websites to collect information that helps us provide our Products to you and to learn how our Products is used. We also use these technologies to help deliver promotional messages and ads for relevant Tiertime products and services.

Cookies are small data files that a web site you visit may save on your hard drive. They usually include an anonymous unique identifier. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive or pass on computer viruses.

These cookies are necessary to enable you to move around our web site and use its features. Without these cookies, we can’t provide services you have asked for, like processing an order in the web store.

We use other cookies to help recognize and remember you when you are logged into the Service so we can remember your settings and preferences, such as your language and region or your logged-in state. These cookies also may help us provide services you have asked for, such as watching a video or commenting on our user forum. These cookies do not track your browsing activity on non-Tiertime websites.

You may disable any of these functional cookies; but if you do so, then various functions of the web site may be unavailable to you or may not work as intended.

### What Is Tiertime’s Approach to Information Collected From Children?

Tiertime does not knowingly collect personal information from children without parental consent. If we learn that we have inadvertently obtained information in violation of applicable laws prohibiting collection of information from children without such consent, we will promptly delete it.

### Will Tiertime Contact Me?

From time to time, we may contact you with information about product announcements, service offerings that we think may be beneficial to you, software updates and special offers. We also may contact you with information about products and services from our business partners. We consider your acceptance of this Privacy Policy as your acceptance of our offer to send you these communications.

## II. Information Access and Disclosure

### Does Tiertime Share My Personal Information?

Tiertime is not in the business of selling or renting your information. We only disclose your information – and then only the minimum information necessary – when:

  * We have your explicit consent to share the information.
  * We need to share your information with service providers who process data on our behalf in order to operate the Products, complete your payment transactions, and help us communicate with you as described elsewhere in this policy; these providers are subject to strict data protection requirements in keeping with our commitments under our US-EU and US-Switzerland Safe Harbor certifications.
  * We need to share your information with service providers to fulfill your product or service requests, including sales, delivery and support requests.
  * We need to share your information with resellers of a Paid Service or product in order to ensure accuracy in the payment for such Paid Service or product, the management of your account and the delivery of your purchase and related support services.
  * We believe it is necessary to investigate potential violations of our Terms of Service, to enforce the Terms of Service, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud or potential threats against persons, property or the systems on which we operate the Service.
  * We determine that the access, preservation or disclosure of information is required or permitted by law to protect the rights, property or personal safety of Tiertime and users of the Service, or is required to comply with applicable laws, including compliance with warrants, court orders or other legal process.

We do not share your account information or user activity history with third parties for the purpose of enabling them to deliver their advertisements to you.

### Does Tiertime Access or Review My Data?

As a rule, Tiertime employees do not monitor or view your personal information, but we list below the limited circumstances in which our employees may need to access or review your personal information:

  * We believe our Product has been violated and confirmation is required or we otherwise have an obligation to review your account as described in our Terms of Service;
  * We need to do so in order to respond to your request for support;
  * Where necessary to protect the rights, property or personal safety of Tiertime and its users (including to protect against potential spam, malware or other security concerns); or
  * In order to comply with our legal obligations, such as responding to warrants, court orders or other legal process. We vigilantly protect the privacy of your account information and, whenever we determine it possible, we provide you with notice if we believe we are compelled to comply with a third party’s request for information about your account.

Last but not least, as part of our efforts to protect your account and the functionality of the Product, our automated systems may analyze the emails you send to and from your Tiertime service account to detect spam, malware or other potential security concerns and may block delivery of such emails.

### Does Tiertime Ever Make Any of My Personal Information Public?

No. Please note, however, that certain portions of the Service, such as user posts designated as “public” and our user forum, are open to any online viewer. Any information that you post in these locations can be read, collected and used by anyone and could enable others to send you unsolicited messages. Tiertime enables you to determine whether or not to post personal or otherwise sensitive information to publicly accessible areas of our site, so you should carefully consider how you use the Product. Tiertime is not responsible for any publication or use of any Personal Information you choose to post in these locations.

## III. Data Storage and Transfer

### Where Is My Data Stored?

When you use Tiertime Software on your computing device, such as by using one of our downloadable applications, Content you save will be stored locally on that device. When you upload your data or information to Tiertime’s website, the information will be replicated on our servers, which are located in the cloud service that Tiertime chooses.

Please be aware that Personal Information and Content submitted to Tiertime will be transferred to a data center provided by cloud service provider. If you store information in or submit data to the Tiertime website or Tiertime Software and sync such Tiertime Software with the Tiertime service, you are confirming your consent to such information, including Personal Information and Content, being transmitted to, hosted and accessed in the cloud.

### How Can I Access or Correct Information Tiertime Holds About Me?

If you wish to (i) access any Personal Information that we hold about you; (ii) request that we correct or delete the Personal Information that we hold about you; or (iii) request that we not use or stop using your Personal Information for marketing purposes, you may contact us via email at tiertime AT Tiertime DOT net. We will comply with such requests to the extent required by law or our policies, and subject to any limitations in our systems.

### How Secure Is My Data?

Tiertime is committed to protecting the security of your information and takes reasonable precautions to protect it. However, internet data transmissions, cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and as a result, we cannot ensure the security of information during its transmission between you and us; accordingly, you acknowledge that you do so at your own risk.

Once we receive your data, we protect it on our servers using a combination of administrative, physical and logical security safeguards. The security of the information stored locally in the Tiertime Software installed on your computing device is dependent upon you making use of the security features on your device. We recommend that you take the appropriate steps to secure all computing devices that you use with the Tiertime software and the Tiertime service.

If Tiertime learns of a security system breach, we may attempt to notify you and provide information on protective steps, if available, through the email address that you have provided to us or by posting a notice on our web site and/or via other communication platforms. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive such notices in writing.

### What Happens If I Want to Stop Using Tiertime?

If you deactivate your account, the Content in your account will not be deleted unless you purposely delete that information, and sync your account before you deactivate your account.

### What Happens If Tiertime Closes My Account?

If Tiertime deactivates your Tiertime service account due to a Terms of Service violation, then you may contact Tiertime to request deletion of your data, and Tiertime will evaluate such requests on a case by case basis, pursuant to our legal obligations.

## IV. Contact Us

### How Can I Contact Tiertime?

Tiertime welcomes your feedback regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have questions, comments or concerns about this Policy, please contact us by email at privacy@ Tiertime.net or postal mail at: Tiertime Corporation, 1765 Landess Avenue, #338, Milpitas, CA 95035, USA.
